A Finding Aid to the C. J. (Clarence Joseph) Bulliet Papers, circa 1888-1959, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bullclar
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1919-1952; Series 4; 20 Linear feet Boxes 5-24
  - Chassaing, Olga, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Chasserain, Theodore, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Chataignier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Chavannes, Puvis de, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Cheney, Russell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Cheskin, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Cheskin, Mrs. Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Cheyne, Ian A. J., 1932 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Choultse, Iwan F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Christensen, Ingeborg, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Christensen, Irving, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Christie, A. U., 1931 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Christie, G. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Chrostowski, Stanislav Ostoja, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Chubknovsky, Boris, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Ciardi, Emma, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Cikovsky, Nicolai, 1931-1938 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Cilfone, Gianni L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Cima da Conegliano, Giovanni, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Cimiotti, Gustave, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Claesz, Pieter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Claghorn, Joseph C., 1932 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Clapp, Marcia, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Clark, Allan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Clark, Alson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Clark, Roland, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Clarke, Virginia Keep, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Clark, Wallish, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Clarke, Harry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Clarke, John L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Clarkson, Ralph, 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Clausen, George, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Clays, P.J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Cleef, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Clements, Gabrielle DeV., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Clerck, Jan de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Clime, Warfield Scott, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Clivette, Merton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Clouet, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Clusmann, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Coats, Randolph La Salle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Coe, Ethel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Coen, Eleanor, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Coffin, Haskell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Cohen, Max Bernd, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Cohen, Peter, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Cohn, Max, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Cole, Timothy, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Coleman, Glenn O., 1929-1940 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Collier, John, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Collins, Roy H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Colnot, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Colom, Joan, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Colwell, Elizabeth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Combs, Enid, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Comins, Eben F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Conkling, Mabel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Conner, G. D., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Connor, Jerome, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Conor, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Conrow, Wilford S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Constable, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Conti, Gino E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Conway, Fred, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Cook, Charlie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Cook, Hazelle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Cook, Howard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Cooper, Colin Campbell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Cooper, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Copeland, Lila, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Copley, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Copley, John Singleton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Coppedge, Fern I., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Coppini, Pompeo Luigi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Corazzo, Alexander, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Corbino, Jon, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Corcos, Lucille, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Cordrey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Cornelisz von Amsterdam, Jacob, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Cornell, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Cornwell, Dean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Corot, Jean Baptiste, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Correggio, Antonio da, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Cortez, E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Cortis, Antonio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Corwin, Charles Abel, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Cosimo, Piero di, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Costigan, John E., 1937 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cosway, Richard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Coter, Colyn de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cotes, Francis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cottet, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cotton, William H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Courbet, Gustave, 1936-1941 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Court, Emily, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Couse, E. Irving, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Covarrubias, Miguel, 1935-1936 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Covey, Arthur, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Covington, Wickliffe C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Cowan, Bertha, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cowan, E. Van Osdel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Cowels, Russell, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Cox, Charles M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Cox, Kenyon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Cox-McCormack, Nancy, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Cox, Gardner, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Cox, H. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Coxon, Raymond, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Cramer, Florence Ballin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Cramer, Konrad, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Cranach, Lucas, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Crane, Bruce, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Creighton, Bessy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Crespin, L. Ch., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Cresson, Margaret French, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Crisler, Richard M., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Crist, Richard H., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Crivelli (school of), circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Crome, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Crooks, Mildred, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Cropsey, J. F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Crossan, Orpha, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Crow, L. A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Crunelle, Leonard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Cuernavaca, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Curnock, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Curran, C. C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Curry, John Steuart, 1933-1939 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Cuyp, Aelbert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Cybis, Boleslaw, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Cykowski, Casimirde, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Dabrowski, Adam, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Dagoty, J.B.A. Gautier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Dahlgreen, Charles, 1928-1935 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Dahlquist, Edward, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Daingerfield, Elliot, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Dali, Salvador, 1934-1941 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Dallin, Cyrus E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Dalstrom, Gustaf, 1930-1935 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Damianakes, Cleo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Daniel, Lewis C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Daniell, W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Darge, Fred, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Dasberg, Andrew, 1927-1931 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Daubigny, Charles François, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Daugherty, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Daumier, Honore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Davey, Randall, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - David, Hermine, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - David, Jacques Louis, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Davidson, Jo, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Davidson, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Davies, Arthur B., 1923-1935 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Da Vinci, Leonardo, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Davis, Cecil Clark, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Davis, Charles H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Davis, Lew E., 1937 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Davis, Pauline Graff, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Davis, Stark, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Davis, Stuart, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Davis, Warren, 1924-1929 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Dawson, Montague, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - De Amicis, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Dean, Helga Haugan, 1935-1939 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Deane, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Dearth, Henry Golden, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - deBeers, Florence C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - DeBelle, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Deberitz, Per, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Debucourt, Philibert Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - De Camps, A.G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - De Chirico, Giorgio, 1930-1943 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - De Creeft, Jose, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Deering, Charles, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - De Fiori, Ernesto, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Defregger, F. V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Degas, Edgar, 1936-1941 (Box 9, Folder 92-94)
  - Dehn, Adolf, 1934-1937 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Deinka, Alexandre, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - De Koven, Seymour, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Delacroix, Eugene, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Del Biondo, Giovanni, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Delbos, Julius, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Delgado, Santiago Martinez, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Della Robbia, Andrea, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Della Robbia, Luca, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Del Piombo, Sebastiano, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - De Lyon, Corneille, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - De Maio, Salvatore, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - De Martelly, John S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Demuth, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Denton, Donald, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Depero, Fortunato, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Derain, Andre, 1928-1941 (Box 9, Folder 111-112)
  - Derjinsky, Gleb, circa 1888-1959 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Deschamp, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Deshayes, Jean Baptiste, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Desiderio da Settignano, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Despaiu, Charles, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - D'Espagnat, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Desrue, Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Detwiller, Frederick K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Deutsch, Boris, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - De Val, P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Devera, Jean Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Devis, A. W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - De Vos, Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dewing, Thomas Wilmer, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Dey, Mukul Chandra, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - De Young, Harry Anthony, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dezire, Henri, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - D'Hue, Lambertus, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Diaz, Daniel Vazquez, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Diaz de la Pena, Narcisse Virgle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Di Bonomo, Jacobello, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Dick, Roosevelt, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Dickinson, Edwin E., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Dickinson, Preston, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Dickinson, Sidney, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Di Credi, Lorenzo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Diederich, William Hunt, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Diego, Julio de, 1935-1949 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Diem, Peter Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Dieterle, Marie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Dietz, Greta Allen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Dievenbach, H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Di Francisci, Anthony, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Diggs, Arthur, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Dillens, Julien, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Dimroch, Ethel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Dinet, Etienne, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Disney, Walt, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Dix, Eulabee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Dix, Otto, 1934-1938 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Dixon, Maynard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Dixon, Mildred Sartelle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Dobson, Frank, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Doctoroff, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Dodd, Lamar, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Dodd, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Dodge, William De Leftwich, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Domaradski, Stephan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Donaldson, Elise, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Donatello (Bottega of), circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Dongen, Kees van, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Donghi, Antonio, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Donnelly, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Donovan, C. V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Doogevaard, Jacob, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Dornbush, A. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Dottori, Gerardo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Dou, Gerard, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Doucet, Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Dougherty, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Douglas, E. Bruce, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Douglass, Lucille, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Douthat, Milton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Dove, Arthur G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Drabinowicz, Stanley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Desles, Albert, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Drew, Dorothy, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Drew, Elbert G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Driggs, Elsie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Driver, Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Drudis-Biada, Jose, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Drumaux, Angelina, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Drury, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Duble, Lee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Dubordieu, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Du Bois, Guy Pene, 1930-1940 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Duchamp, Marcel, 1927-1936 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Duchamp-Villon, Raymond, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Dudley, Frank V., 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Dudley, Katharine, 1934-1945 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Dufner, Edward, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Dufrency, Georges, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Dufresne, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Dufy, Raoul, 1931-1941 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Dulac, Marguerite, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Du Maurier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Dumonstier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Dupre, Jules, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Durer, Albrecht, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Durieux, Caroline, 1936-1939 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Duveneck, Frank, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Duvivier, Aimee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Dwight, Mabel, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Dyer, Briggs, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Dyer, Nancy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Dykaar, Moses Wainer, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Dyson, Will, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Eakins, Thomas, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Earl, Ralph, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Earle, Cornelia, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Eastman, William J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Eaton, J. H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Eberle, Abasentia St. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Ebrle, T. L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ebert, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Ebihara, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Eby, Kerr, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Eddy, Henry S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Edgerly, Beatrice, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Edmonson, William J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Edwards, George Wharton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Edwards, Maebel Perry, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Edwards, Nancy Bixby, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Edzard, Dietz, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Eekman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Egan, Ben F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Egas, Camilio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Egeli, Bjorn, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Eilshemius, Louis, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Eisner, Dorothy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Eldred, H. B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - El Greco, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Eliasoph, Paula, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Elipe, Luis Berdejo, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Elliott, James, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Ellis, Dean, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Elmer, Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Emerson, Louise H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Emerson, W. C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Emrich, Harvey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Emslie, Rosalie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Engelhard, Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Engelmann, William J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Engers, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Engert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Engle, H. R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - English, Betty, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - English, Harold, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Ennis, George Pearce, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Ensor, James and Edvard Munch, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Enters, Angna, 1933-1952 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Epperly, Richard R., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Epping, Franc, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Epstein, Jacob, 1925-1933 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Erffa, H. N., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Erickson, J. Seaverns, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Erickson, Norman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Ernst, Max, 1939-1942 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Esherick, Wharton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Eskridge, Robert Lee, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Etnier, Stephen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Eugen, Prince, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Evans, Dulah Llan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Evansmith, H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Everett, Ethel Walton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - Everett, Walker, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Evergood, Philip, 1935-1940 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Fabion, Jan, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Fabion, John, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Fackert, William Oscar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Faed, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Fagen, Barbara, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Faggi, Alfeo, 1931-1947 (Box 10, Folder 162-163)
  - Faistauer, Anton, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Falls, C. B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - Fantin-Latour, Henri, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Farge, Henri, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Farnsworth, Jerry, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - Farre, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 169)
  - Faucet, Mrs., circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - Faulkner, Barry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 171)
  - Fay, Clark, circa 1888-1959 (Box 10, Folder 172)
  - Fechin, Nicolai, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Feher, Joseph, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Feininger, Lyonel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Feke, Robert, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Fellers, Annette, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fenelle, Stanford, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fenton, Beatrice, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ferat, Serge, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ferg, Franz Parre, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Ferguson, Duncan, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ferrazzi, Ferruccio, 1926-1931 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Feru, Hortense, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Feuerbach, Anselm, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Fidler, Harry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Field, Jessie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Fiene, Ernest, 1935-1941 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Firle, Walther, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Fisher, Fry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Fiske, Gertrude, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Fitsch, Eugene C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Fitton, Hedley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Fjaestad, Maja, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Fjelde, Paul, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Flagg, James Montgomery, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Flanagan, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Flannagan, John B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Fleck, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Fletcher, F. Morley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Flink, Govert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Flint, W. Russell, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Fliport, Charles Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Florsheim, Richard Aberle, 1940-1951 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Folinsbee, John F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Foote, Will Howe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Forain, Jean Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Forbes, Vivian, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Ford, Lauren, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Ford, Ruth van Sickle, 1932-1950 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Forkner, Edgar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Fornari, A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Forsberg, Elmer A., 1935 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Forsyth, W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Fortess, Karl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Foujita, 1937-1941 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Fould, Achille, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Fournier, Alexis Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Fournier, Gabriel, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Fox, Seymour, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Foy, Frances, 1927-1939 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Fragonard, Jean Honore, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Frain, H. N., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Frank, Gerald A., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Frank, Raoul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Franklin, Dwight, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Fraser, James Earle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Free, Karl, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Freed, Ernest, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Freeman, Don, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Frelant, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Freman, Agnes V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - French, Daniel Chester, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Fresnage, Roger de la, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Frey, Erwin F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Friedel, Albert H., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Friedman, Arnold, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Friedman, Mrs. J. K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Friedman, Martin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Friend, Shirley, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Frieseke, Frederick Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Friesz, Emile Othan, 1924-1929 (Box 11, Folder 70)